Guide to Records of the Office of the President (John Brademas) RG.3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series XIV. Correspondence, 1981-1990; 1983-1986; 152942; 3.30 Linear Feet in 8 manuscript boxes.
  - D -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152993 (Box 246, Folder 5)
  - E -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152992 (Box 246, Folder 6)
  - F -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152991 (Box 246, Folder 7)
  - G -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152990 (Box 246, Folder 8)
  - H -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152989 (Box 246, Folder 9)
  - I -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152988 (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - J -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152987 (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - K -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152986 (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - L -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152985 (Box 247, Folder 4)
  - Ma-Md -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152984 (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - Me-Mz -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152983 (Box 247, Folder 6)
  - N -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152982 (Box 247, Folder 7)
  - O -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152981 (Box 247, Folder 8)
  - P -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152980 (Box 247, Folder 9)
  - Q -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152979 (Box 248, Folder 1)
  - R -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152978 (Box 248, Folder 2)
  - Sa-Sh -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152977 (Box 248, Folder 3)
  - Si-Sz -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152976 (Box 248, Folder 4)
  - T -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152975 (Box 248, Folder 5)
  - U -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152974 (Box 248, Folder 6)
  - V -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152973 (Box 248, Folder 7)
  - W -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152972 (Box 248, Folder 8)
  - XYZ -- Alphabetical File, 1985-1986; 152971 (Box 248, Folder 9)
  - July, 1985 (Box 253, Folder 1-2)
  - August, 1985 (Box 253, Folder 3)
  - A -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152970 (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - Ba-Bn -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152969 (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - Bo-Bz -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152968 (Box 249, Folder 3)
  - C -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152967 (Box 249, Folder 4-5)
  - D -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152966 (Box 249, Folder 6)
  - E -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152965 (Box 249, Folder 7)
  - F -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152964 (Box 250, Folder 1)
  - G -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152963 (Box 250, Folder 2)
  - H -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152962 (Box 250, Folder 3)
  - I -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152961 (Box 250, Folder 4)
  - J -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152960 (Box 250, Folder 5)
  - K -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152959 (Box 250, Folder 6)
  - L -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152958 (Box 250, Folder 7-8)
  - Ma-Md -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152957 (Box 251, Folder 1)
  - Me-Mz -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152956 (Box 251, Folder 2)
  - N -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152955 (Box 251, Folder 3)
  - O -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152954 (Box 251, Folder 4-5)
  - P -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152953 (Box 251, Folder 6)
  - Q -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152952 (Box 251, Folder 7)
  - R -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152951 (Box 251, Folder 8-9)
  - S-Sh Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152950 (Box 252, Folder 1)
  - Si-Sz -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152949 (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - T -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152948 (Box 252, Folder 3)
  - U -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152947 (Box 252, Folder 4)
  - V -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152946 (Box 252, Folder 5)
  - W -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152945 (Box 252, Folder 6)
  - XYZ -- Alphabetical File, 1983-1984; 152944 (Box 252, Folder 7)
  - Memos from Brademas, 1981 (Box 253, Folder 4)
  - Letters to Brademas, 1984-1990 (Box 253, Folder 5)
  - Letters from Brademas, 1988-1990 (Box 253, Folder 6)